<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidDemoProject</string>
    <string name="recycler_view">Recycler View</string>
    <string name="image_of_the_planet">Image of the planet</string>
    <string name="planet_list">Planet List</string>
    <string name="affirmation1">I am strong.</string>
    <string name="affirmation2">I believe in myself.</string>
    <string name="affirmation3">Each day is a new opportunity to grow and be a better version of myself.</string>
    <string name="affirmation4">Every challenge in my life is an opportunity to learn from.</string>
    <string name="affirmation5">I have so much to be grateful for.</string>
    <string name="affirmation6">Good things are always coming into my life.</string>
    <string name="affirmation7">New opportunities await me at every turn.</string>
    <string name="affirmation8">I have the courage to follow my heart.</string>
    <string name="affirmation9">Things will unfold at precisely the right time.</string>
    <string name="affirmation10">I will be present in all the moments that this day brings.</string>
    <string name="delete_affirmation">Delete Affirmation</string>
    <string name="delete_todo">Delete Todo</string>
    <string name="edit_todo">Edit todo</string>
    <string name="a_la_carte_kitchen">A La Carte Kitchen</string>
    <string name="scroll_to_top">Scroll to top</string>
    <string name="movie1_title">Iron Man</string>
    <string name="movie1_rating">7.9</string>
    <string name="movie1_year">2008</string>
    <string name="movie1_plot">After being held captive in an Afghan cave, billionaire engineer Tony Stark creates a unique weaponized suit of armor to fight evil.</string>
    <string name="movie2_title">The Incredible Hulk</string>
    <string name="movie2_rating">6.7</string>
    <string name="movie2_year">2008</string>
    <string name="movie2_plot">Bruce Banner, a scientist on the run from the U.S. Government, must find a cure for the monster he turns into, whenever he loses his temper.</string>
    <string name="movie3_title">Iron Man 2</string>
    <string name="movie3_rating">7.0</string>
    <string name="movie3_year">2010</string>
    <string name="movie3_plot">With the world now aware of his identity as Iron Man, Tony Stark must contend with both his declining health and a vengeful mad man with ties to his father\'s legacy.</string>
    <string name="movie4_title">Thor</string>
    <string name="movie4_rating">7.0</string>
    <string name="movie4_year">2011</string>
    <string name="movie4_plot">The powerful but arrogant god Thor is cast out of Asgard to live amongst humans in Midgard (Earth), where he soon becomes one of their finest defenders.</string>
    <string name="movie5_title">Captain America: The First Avenger</string>
    <string name="movie5_rating">6.9</string>
    <string name="movie5_year">2011</string>
    <string name="movie5_plot">Steve Rogers, a rejected military soldier transforms into Captain America after taking a dose of a Super-Soldier serum. But being Captain America comes at a price as he attempts to take down a war monger and a terrorist organization.</string>
    <string name="movie6_title">The Avengers</string>
    <string name="movie6_rating">8.0</string>
    <string name="movie6_year">2012</string>
    <string name="movie6_plot">Earth\'s mightiest heroes must come together and learn to fight as a team if they are going to stop the mischievous Loki and his alien army from enslaving humanity.</string>
    <string name="movie7_title">Iron Man 3</string>
    <string name="movie7_rating">7.2</string>
    <string name="movie7_year">2013</string>
    <string name="movie7_plot">When Tony Stark\'s world is torn apart by a formidable terrorist called the Mandarin, he starts an odyssey of rebuilding and retribution.</string>
    <string name="movie8_title">Thor: The Dark World</string>
    <string name="movie8_rating">6.9</string>
    <string name="movie8_year">2013</string>
    <string name="movie8_plot">When the Dark Elves attempt to plunge the universe into darkness, Thor must embark on a perilous and personal journey that will reunite him with doctor Jane Foster.</string>
    <string name="movie9_title">Captain America: The Winter Soldier</string>
    <string name="movie9_rating">7.8</string>
    <string name="movie9_year">2014</string>
    <string name="movie9_plot">As Steve Rogers struggles to embrace his role in the modern world, he teams up with a fellow Avenger and S.H.I.E.L.D agent, Black Widow, to battle a new threat from history: an assassin known as the Winter Soldier.</string>
    <string name="movie10_title">Avengers: Age of Ultron</string>
    <string name="movie10_rating">7.3</string>
    <string name="movie10_year">2015</string>
    <string name="movie10_plot">When Tony Stark and Bruce Banner try to jump-start a dormant peacekeeping program called Ultron, things go horribly wrong and it\'s up to Earth\'s mightiest heroes to stop the villainous Ultron from enacting his terrible plan.</string>
    <string name="movie11_title">Ant-Man</string>
    <string name="movie11_rating">7.3</string>
    <string name="movie11_year">2015</string>
    <string name="movie11_plot">Armed with a super-suit with the astonishing ability to shrink in scale but increase in strength, cat burglar Scott Lang must embrace his inner hero and help his mentor, Dr. Hank Pym, plan and pull off a heist that will save the world.</string>
    <string name="movie12_title">Captain America: Civil War</string>
    <string name="movie12_rating">7.8</string>
    <string name="movie12_year">2016</string>
    <string name="movie12_plot">Political involvement in the Avengers\' affairs causes a rift between Captain America and Iron Man.</string>
    <string name="movie13_title">Thor: Ragnarok</string>
    <string name="movie13_rating">7.9</string>
    <string name="movie13_year">2017</string>
    <string name="movie13_plot">Thor (Chris Hemsworth) is imprisoned on the planet Sakaar, and must race against time to return to Asgard and stop Ragnarök, the destruction of his world, at the hands of the powerful and ruthless villain Hela (Cate Blanchett).</string>
    <string name="movie14_title">Black Panther</string>
    <string name="movie14_rating">7.3</string>
    <string name="movie14_year">2018</string>
    <string name="movie14_plot">T\'Challa, heir to the hidden but advanced kingdom of Wakanda, must step forward to lead his people into a new future and must confront a challenger from his country\'s past.</string>
    <string name="movie15_title">Avengers: Infinity War</string>
    <string name="movie15_rating">8.5</string>
    <string name="movie15_year">2018</string>
    <string name="movie15_plot">The Avengers and their allies must be willing to sacrifice all in an attempt to defeat the powerful Thanos before his blitz of devastation and ruin puts an end to the universe.</string>
    <string name="movie16_title">Ant-Man and the Wasp</string>
    <string name="movie16_rating">7.1</string>
    <string name="movie16_year">2018</string>
    <string name="movie16_plot">As Scott Lang balances being both a Super Hero and a father, Hope van Dyne and Dr. Hank Pym present an urgent new mission that finds the Ant-Man fighting alongside The Wasp to uncover secrets from their past.</string>
    <string name="movie17_title">Avengers: Endgame</string>
    <string name="movie17_rating">8.5</string>
    <string name="movie17_year">2019</string>
    <string name="movie17_plot">After the devastating events of Avengers: Infinity War (2018), the universe is in ruins. With the help of remaining allies, the Avengers assemble once more in order to reverse Thanos\' actions and restore balance to the universe.</string>
    <string name="release_year">Release Year:</string>
    <string name="rating">Rating:</string>
    <string name="plot">Plot</string>
    <string name="example_phone_number">+91 93271 14805</string>
    <string name="example_name">Ankit Verma</string>
    <string name="example_initial_name">A</string>
    <string name="replace_old_list_with_new_list">Replace old list with new list</string>
    <string name="movie_poster">movie poster</string>
    <string name="percent_symbol">%</string>
    <string name="ad_image">Ad Image</string>
    <string name="ad">Ad:</string>
    <string name="amazon">Amazon</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="calls">Calls</string>
    <string name="chats">Chats</string>
    <string name="contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="call">Call</string>
</resources>